{
    "1": {
        "question": "Amazon simple storage service S3 is an object storage suitable for the storage of flat files like Microsoft Word documents, photos, etc.",
        "answer": "T"
    },
    "2": {
        "question": "Amazon S3 replicates all objects ____. (Select the best answer).",
        "options": {
            "A": "On multiple volumes within an availability zone.",
            "B": "In multiple Availability zones within the same region.",
            "C": "Across multiple regions for higher durability.",
            "D": "On multiple S3 buckets."
        },
        "answer": "B"
    },
    "3": {
        "question": "Which of the following can be used as a storage class for an S3 object lifecycle policy?",
        "options": {
            "A": "S3 Standard Access.",
            "B": "AWS Storage Gateway.",
            "C": "S3 Infrequent Access.",
            "D": "Simple Storage Service Glacier.",
            "E": "E. S3 Reduced Redundancy Storage.",
            "F": "F. Amazon Dynamo DB."
        },
        "question_type": "multiple_select",
        "answer": [
            "A",
            "C",
            "D"
        ]
    },
    "4": {
        "question": "The name of an S3 bucket must be unique.",
        "options": {
            "A": "Worldwide across all AWS accounts.",
            "B": "Within a region.",
            "C": "Across all your AWS accounts.",
            "D": "Within your AWS account."
        },
        "answer": "A"
    },
    "5": {
        "question": "You can use amazon elastic file system efc to: (Select the best answer).",
        "options": {
            "A": "Provide simple, scalable, elastic file storage for use only within AWS.",
            "B": "Implement storage for Amazon EC2 instances that multiple virtual machines can access at the same time.",
            "C": "Host a robust CDN to deliver entire web sites with dynamic, static, and streaming content.",
            "D": "Generate user specific content."
        },
        "answer": "B"
    },
    "6": {
        "question": "Amazon Elastic Block Storage (Amazon EBS) is recommended when data ______ and _______ (Choose two).",
        "options": {
            "A": "Requires object level storage.",
            "B": "Must be quickly accessbile, requiring long-term persistence.",
            "C": "Requires an encryption solution.",
            "D": "Needs to be stored in a different availability zone than the one the EC2 instance is in."
        },
        "question_type": "multiple_select",
        "answer": [
            "B",
            "C"
        ]
    },
    "7": {
        "question": "True or false, by default all data stored in amazon S3 is viewable by the public.",
        "answer": "F"
    },
    "8": {
        "question": "Regarding amazon S3 glacier, what is a vault?",
        "options": {
            "A": "The rules that determine who may (or may not) access archives.",
            "B": "An object (photos, videos, files, or documents).",
            "C": "A container for storing archives.",
            "D": "A policy that identifies who can access content stored in Glacier."
        },
        "answer": "C"
    },
    "9": {
        "question": "True or false. When you create a bucket in amazon S3, it is associated with a specific aws region.",
        "answer": "T"
    },
    "10": {
        "question": "Which of the following are features of Amazon Elastic Block Store (Amazon EBS). (Choose two).",
        "options": {
            "A": "Data on an Amazon EBS volume is lost when the attatched instance is stopped.",
            "B": "Amazon EBS volumes can be encrypted transparently to workloads on the attached instance.",
            "C": "Amazon EBS data is automatically backed up to tape.",
            "D": "Data stored on Amazon EBS is automatically replicated within an Availability Zone."
        },
        "question_type": "multiple_select",
        "answer": [
            "B",
            "D"
        ]
    }
}